Finding Aid for Michigan Natural Areas Council Records, 1938-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Site Files undated, 1934-1989 (Box 5)
  - Sleeping Bear Dunes
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - A Natural History of the Sleeping Bear Dunes Country, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Reports and Writings (Box 12)
    - General (Box 12)
  - Smith Woods (Box 12)
  - South Manitou Island (Box 12)
  - Southfield Nature Center (Box 12)
  - Southfield Park Prairie (Box 12)
  - Sprinkler Lake (Box 12)
  - Stonebrook Woodland (Box 12)
  - Stony Creek
    - Cedar Swamp (Box 12)
    - Sheldon Forest (Box 12)
  - Swartz Creek Park (Box 12)
  - Sylvania (Box 12)
  - Tahquamenon State Park (Box 12)
  - Timberland Swamp (Box 12)
  - Teeple Lake Wetland (Box 12)
  - Tobico Marsh (Box 12)
  - Upper Falls, Sturgeon River and Bacco Gorge 1957 (Box 12)
  - Warren Dunes (Box 12)
  - Warren Woods (Box 12)
  - Waterloo Area (Box 12)
  - Wilderness State Park (Box 12)
  - Winnewa Flood Area (Box 12)
  - Willis C. and Mabel Lee Ward Nature Study Area 1970 (Box 12)
  - Wixom Heronry (Box 12)
  - Woldumar (Box 12)
  - Word Nature Study Area Prairie (Box 12)